Finding Aid for the Lisa See Papers LSC.0564
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Writings by Lisa See
  - Book- The Flower Net (1 of 2), Circa 1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "The Flower Net". Chapters 1-10 and timeline.
  - Book- The Flower Net (2 of 2) (Box 39, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of "The Flower Net". Chapters 11- 25.
  - Book- The Flower Net (1 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript of "The Flower Net". Title page through Chapter 13. Includes a photocopy of a page from the New York Times.
  - Book- The Flower Net (2 of 2) (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript of "The Flower Net". Chapter 14 through "Acknowledgements".
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (1 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (2 of 4) (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (3 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Chapters 13- 18.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (4 of 4) (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript of "On Gold Mountain". Chapters 19 through "Sources".
  - Book- The Flower Net (Box 41, Folder 3-6, Box 42, Folder 1-4)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of The Flower Net.
  - Book- Precious Cargo (Box 46, Folder 1-2)
    Typewritten manuscript for "Precious Cargo" by Monica Highland.
  - Book- Precious Cargo (Box 47, Folder 1, Box 46, Folder 3-5)
  - Book-Precious Cargo (1 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript for "Precious Cargo" by Monica Highland. Page 366 through "October".
  - Book-Precious Cargo (2 of 2) (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript for "Precious Cargo" by Monica Highland. "November" through brief biogragraphy of Monica Highland.
  - Book- Turnaround Year (1 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, for "Turnaround Year" by Monica Highland. Descriptions of major characters followed by title page; "Prologue" through "Book IV October - December".
  - Book- Turnaround Year (2 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, for "Turnaround Year" by Monica Highland. "PROLOGUE New Year's Eve, 1967" through "Book I January - March".
  - Book -Turnaround Year (3 of 3) (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, for "Turnaround Year" by Monica Highland. "Book II April - June".
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, for "110 Shanghai Road". "Prologue 1926" through "Book II 1937". "Book I" ends in the middle of a sentence on page 148.
  - Book- 110 Shanghai Road (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript for "110 Shanghai Road". On title page is "SHANGHAI OUTLINE: BOOKS II - VI by Monica Highland".
  - Book- Lotus Land, 15 Mar 1984 (Box 48, Folder 3-4)
    Typewritten television treatment for Lotus Land written by William Bast.
  - Screenplay- Secrets, 5 Oct 1987 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript for the screenplay "Secrets" by Lisa See and Carolyn See. Also on title page is "Registered: WGAW".
  - Articles - 1997, 1998, 1996-1999 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Untitled manuscripts on various subjects; book reviews; conference paper from the fourteenth annual AAAS conference entitled "Recovering Buried Lives" presented by Aimee Liu and Lisa See. Also includes correspondence with editors.
  - Writers Meet Their Public (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Drafts of a manuscript, extensively edited; handwritten notes.
  - Precious Cargo, circa 1989 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Manuscript entitled "PRECIOUS CARGO OUTLINE"; handwritten notes.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (Box 50, Folder 5-7, Box 51, Folder 1-4)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of On Gold Mountain.
  - Book-"On Gold Mountain" (3 of 7) (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "On Gold Mountain". Chapters 7-8.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain (Box 52, Folder 1-3, Box 51, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, edited, of On Gold Mountain.
  - Book- On Gold Mountain, 24 Aug 1995 (Box 53, Folder 1-4, Box 52, Folder 4-5)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "On Gold Mountain". Also includes letter from Marian Lizzi, Assistant Editor at St. Martin's Press.
  - Articles- TV Guide, 7 Jul 1984; 1 Dec 1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    "Michael Gross of 'Family Ties'" (p. 10); "Shari Belafonte-Harper of 'Hotel'" (p. 20).
  - Articles- TV Guide, 13 Apr 1985 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    "The Prime-Time Baby Boom" (p. 34).
  - Articles, 1981-2001 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Articles in "Publishers Weekly", "TV Guide", and various newspapers; brochure for the "On Gold Mountain" exhibit at the Autry Museum of Western Heritage; German reviews of "On Gold Mountain".
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 11 Mar 1996 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    "'L.A. Times' Offers New Book Show" (p. 14) and "Elizabeth George: An American in Scotland Yard" (p. 38).
  - Book Review- Bazaar, May 1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    "Anchee's Hour" by Anchee Min (p. 86).
  - PW - 1995 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    Untitled manuscripts on books, authors, booksellers, publishing, etc. Also includes two outgoing letters to "Isabell" and "Maureen".
  - JACKETS/Flower Net, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Book jackets for "The Flower Net"; correspondence from publisher.
  - Opera- On Gold Mountain, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Recordings, synopsis and libretto of opera "On Gold Mountain". Also includes reviews and articles about Lisa See and the opera "On Gold Mountain".
  - The Interior/US [1 of 7], 1999 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    Copy-edited manuscript of "Crooked Shadow", an alternate title for "The Interior". Title page through Chapter 7. Also includes correspondence with publisher relating to changes to manuscript and with Warner Bros. relating to copyright information.
  - The Interior/US [2 of 7] (Box 57, Folder 10)
    Copy-edited manuscript of "Crooked Shadow", an alternate title for "The Interior". Chapters 8-15.
  - The Interior/US [3 of 7] (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Copy-edited manuscript of "Crooked Shadow", an alternate title for "The Interior". Chapter 16 through Acknowledgments.
  - The Interior/US [4 of 7], Feb 1999 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Correspondence from Carolyn Marino and Julie Bennett relating to changes to "Crooked Shadow", an alternate title for "The Interior"; version of back cover text; title page for "Inch of Time" by Lisa See, followed by two Chinese proverbs.
  - The Interior/US [5 of 7] (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript of "The Interior". Title page through Chapter 8.
  - The Interior/US [6 of 7] (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of "The Interior". Chapters 9-17.
  - The Interior/US [7 of 7] (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript of "The Interior". Chapter 18 through Acknowledgments.
  - Book- The Interior, 21 May 1999 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Galley pages of "The Interior" with edits and comments written on them. First galley page has "last corrections" handwritten at top.
  - Book- The Interior (1 of 3), 21 Apr 1999 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    Galley pages of "The Interior" with edits. Title page through Chapter 8.
  - Book- The Interior (2 of 3), 21 Apr 1999 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    Galley pages of "The Interior" with edits. Chapters 9-17.
  - Book- The Interior (3 of 3), 21 Apr 1999 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Galley pages of "The Interior" with edits. Chapter 18 through Acknowledgments.
  - Correspondence, 24 May 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Four pages of edits for "The Interior" written by Lisa See for Robin Stamm; five- page fax from editor Anna Dalton-Knott, which was sent back to her by Lisa See along with comments.
  - Book- The Interior (1 of 3) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "The Interior". Title page through Chapter 9.
  - Book- The Interior (2 of 3) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "The Interior". Chapters 10- 18.
  - Book- The Interior (3 of 3) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    Typewritten manuscript, extensively edited, of "The Interior". Chapter 19 through Acknowledgments.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [1 of 6], Apr 1999 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    Correspondence with editor Anna Dalton-Knott relating to edits to "The Interior"; comments from Tom Finnegan to Carolyn Marino sent to Lisa See by Robin Stamm; typewritten manuscript of English edition of "The Interior", title page through Chapter 7.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [2 of 6] (Box 59, Folder 7)
    Typewritten manuscript of English edition of "The Interior". Chapters 8- 16.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [3 of 6] (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Typewritten manuscript of English edition of "The Interior". Chapter 17 through Acknowledgments.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [4 of 6] (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Typewritten manuscript of world edition of "The Interior". Title page through Chapter 9.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [5 of 6] (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Typewritten manuscript of world edition of "The Interior". Chapters 10- 18.
  - The Interior/English/WORLD [6 of 6] (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Typewritten manuscript of world edition of "The Interior". Chapter 19 through Acknowledgments.
  - Book- Lotus Land, 1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Uncorrected proof of "Lotus Land" by Monica Highland.
  - Book- Lotus Land, 1983 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Buffy Sainte-Marie, 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 5, Box 1, Folder 3)
    Untitled manuscript, research material, correspondence, and notes relating to article on Buffy Ste. Marie. See also Box 1, Folder 3.
  - LOTUS LAND, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Handwritten and typewritten drafts, some extensively edited; joint venture agreement between Carolyn See, Lisa See and John Espey dated April 19, 1981; notes.
  - Publishers Weekly, 19 Aug 1983 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Issue of "Publishers Weekly" announcing that Lisa See is the new Western correspondent for "Publishers Weekly" (p. 18). She is listed in the masthead, but with no author attribution within the publication.
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 2 Sep 1983; 9 Sep 1983 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    "The West Coast Writers' Conference" (p.54)
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 23 Sep 1983; 30 Sep 1983; 14 Oct 1983 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    "Norman Cousins" (p. 78); "Speaking for the Evangelical Publishers" (p. 58) and "Chicano Writers: Looking for a Breakout" (p. 94); "Authors Rescue Book by Bringing Back the '60s" (p.41).
  - Publishers Weekly, 21 Oct 1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Issue of "Publishers Weekly" in which Lisa See is listed in the masthead, but with no author attribution within the publication. There is a notice of the upcoming Loyola Marymount University conference "Writing for Your Life" on page 14.
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 28 Oct 1983; 4 Nov 1983; 18 Nov 1983 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    "Local Interest -- in Food and in the Coit Tower -- Sparks Two San Francisco Bay Area Publishers" (p. 34); "How to Get Rock Fans to Buy the Book" (p. 46); "Jack Olsen" (p. 78).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 25 Nov 1983; 23 Dec 1983 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    "The Many Hats of West Coast Publicists" (p. 42) and "NCBA Regional Focuses on Independents' Future" (p. 45); "The Frustrations of Hawaii" (p. 36).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 27 Jan 1984; 2 Mar 1984 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    "A Day in the Life of Hawaii" (p. 38) and "New Directions in Children's Books -- from California" (p. 58); "Del Mar Boasts a Thriving Publishing Community" (p. 66).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 23 Mar 1984; 30 Mar 1984 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    "The Fall of Network: A California Disaster" (p. 28); "Sales Reps 'Tested' Before Selling Title" (p. 40).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 20 Apr 1984; 27 Apr 1984 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    "Blatty Motion Denied in 'N.Y. Times' Suit" (p. 20); "At Nolo Press, Self-Law is the Niche -- and Business is Fine" (p. 66).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 4 May 1984; 25 May 1984; 8 Jun 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    "California Bookseller Sues Crown Books" (p. 13) and "Rath Tells NCBA: A Unified ABA Will Preserve Independents" (p. 36); "Small Presses, Big Book -- and Other Matters" (p. 33); "A Buyer's Guide to 1984 Olympic Books" (p. 48).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 15 Jun 1984; 6 Jul 1984; 27 Jul 1984 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    "June Flaum Singer" (p. 84); "The Search for Publishing Crevices" (p. 26); "Alfred Publishing: Mood Music to Computer Books" (p. 125).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 31 Aug 1984 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    "The Northwest: Reading -- and Publishing in the Rain" (p. 419).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 7 Sep 1984; 28 Sep 1984 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    "Olympic Books Miss the Bronze" (p. 63); "Celebs Are the Key to the Hollywood Book Party" (p. 46) and "'Forgive and Forget' Campaign Aims for Crossover Sales" (p. 85).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 26 Oct 1984; 2 Nov 1984 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    "Travel Stories -- Far Afield and at Home" (p. 42) and "Arthur Hailey" (p. 106); "Heat Wilts Retailers and Reps at San Diego Show" (p. 62).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 9 Nov 1984; 23 Nov 1984; 4 Jan 1985 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    "Emphasis on Sales and Cooperation at NCBA Show" (p. 48); "Tillie Olsen" (p. 76); "Beautiful Art Books by a Self-Confessed 'Snob'" (p. 29).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 25 Jan 1985; 8 Feb 1985 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    "Tout Ca Change -- Past and Future" (p. 70); "'L.A. Times' Names New 'Book Review' Editor" (p. 24).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 1 Mar 1985; 29 Mar 1984; 5 Apr 1985 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    "Onward & Upward with L. Ron Hubbard" (p. 32); "Literacy, Freedom to Publish, Survival of the Book" (p. 33) and "California Specials: Martial Arts, Luxury Estates" (p. 45); "Bay Area Reviewers Present 1984 Awards, Hear of Anarchy and Independence" (p. 17)
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 26 Apr 1985; 31 May 1985; 14 Jun 1985 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    "Bestsellers from the West Need 'A Longer Flight Path'" (p. 56); "The Business of Books Thrives in Denver" (p. 24); "Frederick Praeger" (p. 49).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 28 Jun 1985; 6 Sep 1985; 4 Oct 1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    "Bringing the Word from China for a Quarter-Century" (p. 26); "The West, Too, Can Do Coffee-Table Books" (p. 34); "California Book People Find Safety in Numbers" (p. 60).
  - Articles- Publishers Weekly, 1 Nov 1985; 22 Nov 1985 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    "The Great Outdoors Spurs New Book Projects" (p. 38); "How to Mourn a Lost Lease" (p. 37).
  - Articles- Small Press, May/Jun 1984; Nov/Dec 1984; Nov/Dec 1985 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    "Publishers Group West" (p. 40); "The Great Tradition" (p. 30); "Aboard the 'Queen Mary': The California Regional Trade Show" (p. 50).
  - Article- Sporting Times, Nov 1978 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    "Jackie Hansen Races Against Herself" (p. 14).
  - Article- Dynamic Years, Jan/Feb 1982 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Article- USA Today Life, 3 May 1984 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    "L'Amour Ropes the Wild 12th Century" (section D).
  - Book Review Agreement, 6 Dec 1993; Restricted material. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Book review agreement with the "Washington Post".
  - Book Review Agreement, 2 May 1998; Restricted material. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Book review agreement with the "New York Times."
  - On Gold Mountain manuscript (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - The Flower Net compare manuscript (Box 66, Folder 4-5)
  - The Flower Net design manuscript (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
  - The Flower Net .3 file, 1997 April (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
  - The Flower Net author's galleys, 1997 May (Box 68, Folder 1, Box 67, Folder 5)
  - The Flower Net 1st pass master, 1997 May (Box 68, Folder 2-3)
  - The Flower Net floppy disk (Box 68, Folder 4)
    One 3.5-inch floppy disk. Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Half and Half, circa 1998 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes a photocopy of See's "The Funeral Banquet" from Half and Half and a Publishers Weekly clipping and "Bill of Rights for Persons of Racially Mixed Ancestry."
  - Pop-up Book, circa 2000-2001 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Includes See's proposal for "Many Miles through Single Steps: The story of Chinese immigration to America." Also includes correspondence with becker&mayer!, Ltd. and outlines for Journey of Hope by Kerby Miller and Patricia Mulholland Miller.
  - On Gold Mountain documentary prospectus, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 7-8)
  - Angels Walk LA files, 2001-2003 (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
    These files include the published Angels Walk LA Chinatown guidebook written by See, as well as drafts, proofs, and research notes.
  - Murder in the Museum, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    A fundraiser for the Pacific Asia Museum featured a murder mystery scripted by See. Includes the script and notes on planning the event.
  - Dragon Bones proposal, circa 1999 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Dragon Bones manuscript, 2001 November (Box 69, Folder 6, Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    Box 69 contains chapters 1-9.
    Box 70 contains from chapter 10 through the epilogue.
  - Dragon Bones first draft (Box 70, Folder 3-5)
  - Dragon Bones original manuscript (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Dragon Bones editing notes (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Dragon Bones copyedited manuscript, 2002 August (Box 71, Folder 4-5)
  - Dragon Bones final with Bob and Sandy's corrections (Box 72, Folder 1, Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Dragon Bones #10020 manuscript (Box 72, Folder 2-3)
  - Dragon Bones galleys, 2002 October (Box 72, Folder 4-5)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan early working draft (Box 72, Folder 6, Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan first draft, circa 2004 May (Box 73, Folder 2-3)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan second draft, circa 2004 (Box 73, Folder 4-5)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan final draft, circa 2004, 2005 January (Box 73, Folder 6, Box 74, Folder 1)
    Folder 6 includes correspondence regarding serial pitches.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan copyedited manuscript, 2004 August (Box 74, Folder 2-3)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan setting manuscript, circa 2004 (Box 74, Folder 4-5)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan galleys, 2004 October (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan galleys (Box 75, Folder 1-2)
    This contains the master copy.
  - Snow Flower and the Secret Fan audiobook script, 2005 March (Box 75, Folder 3-4)
  - Peony in Love first draft (Box 75, Folder 5-6)
  - Peony in Love fifth draft (Box 76, Folder 1-2)
  - Peony in Love with edits (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Peony and the Interrupted Dream (Box 76, Folder 5-6)
  - Peony in Love copyedited draft (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - Peony in Love editing notes (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Peony in Love audio script (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Peony in Love revised proofs, 2007 March (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
  - Shanghai Girls first draft (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Shanghai Girls fifth draft (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
  - Shanghai Girls edits and design (Box 78, Folder 5)
    This includes edits from Sandy and interior design proofs for Shanghai Girls.
  - Shanghai Girls copyedited manuscript, 2008 (Box 78, Folder 6, Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Shanghai Girls galleys, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
  - Dreams of Joy first full draft (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
  - Dreams of Joy draft (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
    This manuscript includes Susan Kamil's suggestions.
  - Dreams of Joy draft (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
    This manuscript includes Bob and Lisa's edits.
  - Dreams of Joy draft (Box 81, Folder 1-2)
    This manuscript includes Bob's edits.
- Correspondence
  This series includes personal and professional correspondence and fanmail.
  - Correspondence/Pers. [1 of 3] (Box 7, Folder 6)
    General incoming correspondence.
  - Correspondence/Pers. [2 of 3], 1985-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    General incoming correspondence. Also includes an item addressed to Carolyn See, relating to her novel "Golden Days".
  - Correspondence/Pers. [3 of 3], 1990-1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - P. W. Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Incoming correspondence, primarily from people interviewed for "Publishers Weekly" articles. Also includes a letter not addressed to Lisa See, but mentions her in the text; another letter written by her to Norman Stephens of Warner Brothers.
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [1 of 7], 1995; Thermal paper. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Incoming correspondence relating to the book "On Gold Mountain".
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [2 of 7], 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [3 of 7], 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [4 of 7] (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [5 of 7], 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [6 of 7], 1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Incoming correspondence from students to whom Lisa See spoke about her book "On Gold Mountain".
  - On Gold Mountain/Letters [7 of 7] (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Business cards; envelopes (empty); addresses; photograph of "Waterhouse & Lester Company" building; list entitled "Thank yous".
  - OGM - Paperback Fan Mail, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Incoming correspondence relating to articles, speaking engagements, appearances, etc. Also includes eight letters from 1989 written by Monica Highland to various people and two unsigned letters addressed to Bruce Harris and Peter Jennings.
  - On Gold Mount/Editing Corresp., 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Correspondence between Lisa See and her editors, agent and others, primarily relating to the editing of the book "On Gold Mountain".
  - OGM - St. Martin, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Correspondence primarily with Marian Lizzi, assistant editor at St. Martin's Press, regarding the book "On Gold Mountain".
  - Flower Net Mail [1 of 4], 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Incoming correspondence relating to "The Flower Net".
  - Flower Net Mail [2 of 4], 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Flower Net Mail [3 of 4], 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Incoming correspondence relating to "The Flower Net"; facsimile from Kim Holland of Crest Enterprises to Sandra Dijkstra of Sandra Dijkstra Literary Agency relating to a Chinese comedy entitled "Be There or Be Square".
  - Flower Net Mail [4 of 4], 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Flower Net - letters [1 of 3], 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Flower Net - letters [2 of 3], 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Flower Net - letters [3 of 3], 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Personal [1 of 4], 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    General incoming correspondence. Also includes a postcard to Ray Boy Colomandin from Lisa See; a note to Monica from Clara; postcard to Alexander Kendall from John Espy.
  - Personal [2 of 4], 1979-1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Personal [3 of 4], 1976-1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    General incoming correspondence. Also includes a newspaper clipping of Clara Sturak; postcard to Alexander Kendall from Carolyn See and John Espy; card to Alexander from "Grandma"; postcard to Roy Coleman from Clara.
  - Personal [4 of 4], 1978-1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    General incoming correspondence. Also includes letter from Lisa See to Roy Coleman.
  - Business [1 of 4], 1978-1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    General incoming correspondence. Also includes letters between Mitch Douglas of International Creative Management and various publishers.
  - Business [2 of 4], 1979-1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Incoming correspondence primarily from editors at McCall's and TV Guide. Also includes a letter to Arnold Hano from Kathleen Neumeyer of The Society of Professional Journalists, Sigma Delta Chi.
  - Business [3 of 4], 1979-1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Incoming correspondence primarily in response to articles published in "TV Guide". Also includes biographical material on Lisa See and Carolyn See; letters to Dick and the Writers Guild East from Carolyn See.
  - Business [4 of 4], 1978-1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Outgoing correspondence primarily sent to various magazine editors.
  - PW [1 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)